[{"answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "What is your reaction?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "We don't really know I guess at the moment exactly what has happened here, do we?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Your girlfriend?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Outside with the police.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Where is she now?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I just want everyone to know the truth.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, we know that, Piers, this past Monday, he was brought to an emergency room in order to be evaluated.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "What can we deduce from this case, you think?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "It is a shocking breakdown in the system and from the research I've done, Virginia has had the highest suicide rate in the past 13 years.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "That is a shocking breakdown in the system, isn't it?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Well a part of it is because a lot people see mental health care as being some sort of a luxury.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Why is that in fact in many states being reduced?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "I think it's ...", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Does it not make it difficult if the word that is apparently so offensive is in common parlance amongst the group who say they find it offensive?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I think that there is something when you said for reclaiming language.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "Is he wise to continue using these deeply offensive words even in those communities?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "If you call me a queer?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "That defined myself because of the history, because of what I've been through, because of what queer brothers and sisters been through.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "But you would continue to use that word about yourself?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Nothing offense me.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Do you agree with that Don?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "You didn't know presumably the sexuality of this guy or was he just being angry and defensive thinking of the first that came into his head which is what I suspect was the case?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "It is biased.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "But is it homophobic or he just use homophobic?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "I don't know if the gay community has reasoned up against Alec Baldwin.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Is it right that he becomes the standard bearer of homophobic bigotry?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "I don't think I'm even remotely offended but, you know, should I be?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "When I was about 14.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "In terms of you're own bipolar condition, when did you first realize that's what it was?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "But was that exacerbated, do you think, by the drug taken?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Probably and I had lived from thrill to thrill and I had a certainty about my success which I can look back now and say, \"That was probably part of my manic.\"", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Did it help you become a great actor?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "I am divorced.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Are you married?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "There are two types of people in this world, those who like Neil Diamond and those who don't.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Would you like to talk about that?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I can play anyone with a college education even though I didn't have one.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "You think you can play a psychiatrist in real life?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "You can study over people do you?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "Well, I think for about 100 years one of the political parties has always tried to get a safety net under people and the other party hasn't, and now we have which is an enormous accomplishment and it started with glitches and problems, but I love to remind people that all of our national endeavor started out badly.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Take us to significant issues at the moment, one ObamaCare, obviously been a hell of a mess the rollout, what do you make of that and you think they'll fix it?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well, first of all I don't think the NRA is a villain, and I don't think that the people against the NRA are villains, I believe that's a problem of the press which started with an us-them problem.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "ORGAN: And in terms of the other issue which is the power of the NRA over the gun debate the apparent entrance (ph) of Washington to do anything about that, what is the root through that?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Well, about the only thing I can think of is a I was hoping to save my prisoner and I didn't do it.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "When you yourself see that famous footage, that infamous footage, what goes through your mind even now, 50 years later?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Well, you don't have time to think about anything like that.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "In that moment, what was going through your mind as he burst through that group of people and came at you?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "When I began talking with him, of course, I didn't -- I was talking to him about the murder of officer J.D. Tippit and that time I didn't have clue that he was going to be a suspect in the presidential shooting.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "How did he come over to you?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I agree with my grandpa and the detective in my show.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What do you think about all the conspiracy theories given all the research that you've now done into this?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Capturing (inaudible), I just came back from the school book depository wherein they had found the riffle and they meet the hole around in the window and so forth.", "docId": "131119pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "In what stage before he was shot, did you know that?", "qSentId": 530}]